Ne, állj...
Jó reggelt Nővérkém.
Ébreszthetnél kevésbé félelmetes módon.
Majdnem szívrohamot kaptam tőled.
Beszéltél álmodban. Biztos valami mocskos dologról álmodtál.
Mi?
Beszéltem álmomban?
Biztos valami rosszat álmodhattam.
Ez az!
Maradt még az őszi limitált Dawson gesztenyepudingból még.
Emlékszem tavaly is ez volt. Nagyon jó volt.
Tavaly egyet se ettem belőle.
Akkor ez a puding biztos egy évet várt rád.
Biztos romlott és undorító már.
Én is veszek belőle egyet.
Ó! Akartam még dinnyéskenyeret is. Menj nyugodtan fizetni, majd utolérlek.
Olyan jó lehet neki, hogy minden zsír a mellére megy.
Heló!
110 jen...
103 jen.
Huh?
Száz... három jen.
Ő, száztíz jen lesz.
Száz.... Száz....
Három... Három...
Kér valami mást is?
"Kansai Oden: 60 jen"
Egy haltortát is szeretnék.
Rendicsek...
Ha... Hatv
Hatvan... hatvankét jen lesz.
Még a három százalékos adót is rászámolta.
Kér szatyrot is hozzá?
Igen, kérem.
Legyen szép napja.
Túl sok nasit vettem.
Szeretnél még egy haltortát is Hana?
Persze!
Le kéne feküdnöm.
Ne maradjatok fent sokáig, rendben?
"VALÓS rémisztő történetek"
Oké!
Üdv újra a "100 rémisztő fotó" műsorában.
SZELLEM-AKTÁK:
Különös tapasztalatok
Next up is this photo here.
A beautiful fall scene by the river.
Two campers making happy memories.
It may look perfectly
ordinary at first glance,
"What's lurking in the shadows..."
but you already know
what's lurking in the shadows.
That's right, take a closer look
at what's in the tent...
C'mon, that's totally edited in!
This kind of crap is why
people are pulling the plug.
Right?
Y-Yeah, huh.
We'll have more for you
after the break!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
We'll have more for you
after the break!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
Don't touch that dial,
or you'll be cursed!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
Commercials already?! C'mon, man!
Seriously, this is why
nobody watches TV anymore!
Fragrant, sparkling, and smooth...
I-I'm gonna go get a drink!
Huh? Why?
I'm just kinda thirsty!
Could you get me a soda?
What should I get...
"Warm Red Bean Soup"
It's pretty chilly, so maybe
I'll do a warm red bean soup.
I'll get one for Kyousuke, too.
It'll warm him up.
A tiny old man!
That's the same sort of monster that
celebrities always say they've seen!
They're actually real!
It's kind of cute...
Though maybe I only think that
'cause the others are so gross.
Mmkay.
Whoops, my hand slipped.
Oh, no, it rolled over here...
A giant old man. Wow.
Wh-Why'd I follow it?!
I-It's fine.
I just need to get my money and leave.
Wow, where'd it go?
Hey, there's my 500-yen coin!
S-Slowly, now...
I can't believe it rolled this far.
Slowly, don't panic...
J-Just a little further...
If I run right now,
it might come after me!
I-I gotta hurry!
I-I've gotta get my 500-yen coin...
Why are my hands shaking so bad?!
I have to calm down!
Wh-What the hell?!
I'm gonna cry...
I can't do this!
My 500-yen coin...
W-Wait, come back here with my 500 yen!
I'm saved!
There you are.
Wait, where are the drinks?
My money got stolen
before I could buy anything.
What?! By who?!
--A crow.
--A crow?
Yeah.
Well, I'll go get it back for you!
No, I owe it my life.
Huh?
--Later!
--See you tomorrow!
Bye-bye!
Man, I'm hungry!
Let's go underwear shopping next week!
Sure. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye!
I saw so many scary monsters
at school today.
Hey, where do you
wanna go today? I'm hungry!
Your sister's acting weird?
Yeah.
By weird, like, how weird?
She's sighing a lot,
and just in a weird mood all the time.
And she keeps groaning
"No, please" in her sleep.
Got it! That is weird.
--She's got a boyfriend!
--What?
My big sis acted like that
when she got a boyfriend.
A boyfriend?
--A pure maiden gives her beloved
her whole mind, body, and soul! Y'know?
--Come to think of it,
she made up that whole crow story...
Nope, I don't!
Also, I'm super faithful
when I'm with a guy!
--Could she actually have a boyfriend?!
--Though I've never been with a guy.
If she does, then...
She'd tell me, right?
"Bookstore"
"Paranormal Oddities"
If she has a boyfriend,
then why's she hiding it from me?
Creepy bastard! I won't
let you get away with this!
I'm gonna keep my sister safe!
"Paranormal Oddities"
Don't think this will help...
I think I'm good.
She's leaving?
Is she going to meet up with him now?
What book was she looking at, anyway?
"99 Ways to Please Your Lover"
"Hickeys are a sign of love"
H-Hickeys?
Somehow, I made it through another day.
My sister's in the bath.
Here goes!
That monster in the bookstore
was really scary.
I can't believe I didn't react.
Thankfully, all the ones after that
just stood around doing nothing.
I'm really scared of the ones that hide
or jump out at me, 'cause I might react.
Now I can't go to that bookstore anymore.
I must be tired if
I'm falling asleep in the bath.
No! Not in the bathroom!
Please, anywhere but in here!
I-I've got no choice now.
I'm just gonna have to
get out, a-and quick...
S-Stop!
I can't!
Hey, Sis! I figured I'd join y--
S-Sorry!
Good, she doesn't have any hickeys.
Wait, why am I so embarrassed?
We've taken tons of baths before!
N-Nevermind, I'll take one later.
Kyousuke!
I-I'll wash your back.
Huh? Uh, okay!
Sis, do you have a boyfriend?
Why're you asking?
So you do have one?
No, I don't.
You don't have to hide it from me.
I'm not. I don't have one.
Oh.
How's school?
It's okay.
Every day, when I wake up, I make a wish.
That today, I won't see them.
The weather's so nice today.
I feel like I see more
and more of them, every day.
No, no, think good thoughts!
That's right! I still have
that Chestnut Pudding!
I'll have that this morning!
So for some reason, this crow is her--
Oh, speak of the devil.
You're finally up.
Talk about sleeping late.
Morning, Miko.
I hear you made friends with a crow?
C'mon, eat your breakfast.
You're going to be late.
You don't look so good, Sis.
Didn't get enough sleep?
Did you have a bad dream?
Or did you boyfriend dump you?
I'm kidding.
Boyfriend?
It's 'cause you sleep
with your shirt all hiked up!
Shirt?
You don't have a boyfriend, right?
Boyfriend?
What's wrong, Miko?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
I'm fi...
...ne.
Oh hey, I saw pudding in the fridge.
Is that yours, Sis?
Yeah.
Pudding?
Better put your name on it,
or someone will eat it again.
C'mon, Kyosuke, don't bring that up.
You got into that huge fight with
your dad when he ate yours last year.
Seriously, don't bring it up!
You were so mad,
I thought you were possessed!
Pudding... pudding... pudding...
Thanks for breakfast.
Is that all you're going to eat?
Sorry, I'm just not hungry.
I'm heading out.
Stay safe!
Have a good day!
Pudding.
Miko?
What, forget something?
Sheesh, you need
to double-check sooner, hon.
"Chestnut Pudding"
Wow.
You're giving it to me, Miko?
I'm sorry for eating it last year.
I really wanted to apologize to you,
but I never got the chance.
I never got to make it up to you.
See you later.
Pudding?
No, that's for me!
If you see me, when you see me,
do you see me? Look at me!
You saw? You saw me, right?
You're seeing me, right?
(Feel my wrath,
feel my wrath, feel my wrath!)
(See my blood,
see my blood, see my blood!)
(Fear my grudge,
fear my grudge, fear my grudge!)
(Suffer my curse,
suffer my curse, suffer my curse!)
Turn towards me, baby
C'mon, come closer now
Don't look away, non non non
Look me right in the eye
In the flames, or in the trees,
Or even in your bed
I'll be with you forever
I'll want you forever
I want to haunt you,
I want to rest in peace,
I want to find spiritual release
Give poor, little me
All your comfort
All your offerings
All of your soul
Won't you let me haunt you,
I'm obsessed with you
There's no getting away,
I won't let you escape
Won't you let me haunt you,
my curse will bind you
I'll tie you down
so you can't run away
Won't you let me haunt you,
around the clock
I know you can feel my hand
on your shoulder
Won't you let me haunt you,
turn around
I'm right behind you
If you see me, when you see me,
do you see me? Look at me!
If you can't see me, I'll stay until you see,
until you say you see
If you see me, when you see me,
do you see me? Look at me!
You saw? You saw me, right?
You're seeing me, right?
Welcome back to "100 Horrific Photos."
"GHOST FILES: Extraordinary Experiences"
Next up is this photo here.
A beautiful fall scene by the river.
Two campers making happy memories.
It may look perfectly
ordinary at first glance,
"What's lurking in the shadows..."
but you already know
what's lurking in the shadows.
That's right, take a closer look
at what's in the tent...
C'mon, that's totally edited in!
This kind of crap is why
people are pulling the plug.
Right?
Y-Yeah, huh.
We'll have more for you
after the break!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
We'll have more for you
after the break!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
Don't touch that dial,
or you'll be cursed!
"More after the break!!"
"REAL Scary Stories"
Commercials already?! C'mon, man!
Seriously, this is why
nobody watches TV anymore!
Fragrant, sparkling, and smooth...
I-I'm gonna go get a drink!
Huh? Why?
I'm just kinda thirsty!
Could you get me a soda?
That's not the sort of stuff
kids should be watching.
"I See Them, Too"
You see, not all ghosties
are bad guys!
"I See Them, Too"
So give them a holler
every now and then!
"I See Them, Too"
They might just
talk back!
"I See Them, Too"
Next time, episode 5!
"I See Them, Too!"
"I See Them, Too"
And we'll finally get to see
a new character, too!